Guide to the Daily Worker and the Daily World Negatives Collection PHOTOS.223.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: 4 x 5, 120 and 127 Negatives
  - Housing - Tract Homes Construction., undated; cuid38108 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01062-01 - 01062-06)
  - Housing - Ulmer Park Tenants Council Demonstration against Rent Increase., undated; cuid38109 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01063-01 - 01063-05)
  - Housing Tenants League - Meeting at School, [Don Shek?]., undated; cuid38110 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01064-01 - 01064-07)
  - Housing - Unidentified Demolition., undated; cuid38111 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01065-01 - 01065-06)
  - Individuals - Abt, John., undated; cuid38112 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01066-01)
  - Individuals - Allende, Salvador., undated; cuid38113 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01067-01)
  - Individuals - Amter, Israel., undated; cuid38114 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01068-01 - 01068-03)
  - Individuals - Amter, Israel., undated; cuid38115 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01069-01 - 01069-02)
  - Individuals - Anderson, Mark - AFL-CIO Endorsing Congressmen Anderson at Hotel Pennsylvania (New York, New York)., undated; cuid38116 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01070-01 - 01070-11)
  - Individuals - Armstrong, Henry (boxer)., undated; cuid38117 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01071-01 - 01071-03)
  - Individuals - Bardy's Farewell Party., undated; cuid38118 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01072-01 - 01072-09)
  - Individuals - Barsky, Edward K. - Roosevelt Hotel Banquet (New York, New York)., undated; cuid38119 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01073-01 - 01073-06)
  - Individuals - Bart, Phil., undated; cuid38120 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01074-01 - 01074-04)
  - Individuals - Bethune, Norman., undated; cuid38121 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01075-01)
  - Individuals - Bodenheim, Maxwell., undated; cuid38122 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01076-01)
  - Individuals - Brás, Juan Mari., undated; cuid38123 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01076A-01 - 01076A-02)
  - Individuals - Browder, Earl - Petition for., undated; cuid38124 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01077-01 - 01077-14)
  - Individuals - Browder, Earl - with Seamen under Posters for Freedom of Earl Browder and Anti-Hitler Posters., undated; cuid38125 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01078-01 - 01078-02)
  - Individuals - Browder, Earl - with South African Communist Party Leader., undated; cuid38126 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01079-01 - 01079-02)
  - Individuals - Brown, Arnold (evicted veteran)., undated; cuid38127 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01080-01 - 01080-04)
  - Individuals - Burns, Ester., undated; cuid38128 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01081-01 - 01081-03)
  - Individuals - Burroughs, Charles and Neal., undated; cuid38129 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01082-01 - 01082-02)
  - Individuals - Burroughs, William and Mother Bloor at Parade Organized by the American League Against War and Fascism., undated; cuid38130 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01083-01 - 01083-02)
  - Individuals - Cacchione, Peter V., undated; cuid38131 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01084-01 - 01084-12)
  - Individuals - Cacchione, Peter V. - Ball in Honor of (Sponsored by Peter V. Cacchione Association)., undated; cuid38132 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01085-01 - 01805-05)
  - Individuals - Cacchione, Peter V. - Hearing on Cacchione's Bill, Conference Room at New York City Council., undated; cuid38133 (Box 8b, Shoot-negative 01086-01 - 01086-03)
  - Individuals - [Chelsea?], Martha., undated; cuid38134 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01087-01 - 01087-03)
  - Individuals - [Corriya?], V., undated; cuid38135 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01088-01 - 01088-02)
  - Individuals - Crosbie, Paul., undated; cuid38136 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01089-01)
  - Individuals - Damon, Anna - with Daughter., undated; cuid38137 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01090-01 - 01090-05)
  - Individuals - Danielson, Mary (Brooklyn, New York)., undated; cuid38138 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01091-01 - 01091-04)
  - Individuals - Davidow, Mike., undated; cuid38139 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01092-01 - 01092-08)
  - Individuals - Davis, Angela Y. - Demonstrations for., undated; cuid38140 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01093-01 - 01093-06)
  - Individuals - Davis, Benjamin J. (Benjamin Jefferson) - Sitting on Desk, Reading., undated; cuid38141 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01094-01 - 01094-05)
  - Individuals - Davis, Benjamin J. (Benjamin Jefferson) - Two Women Wearing Benjamin Davis Pins., undated; cuid38142 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01095-01)
  - Individuals - Dennis, Eugene (sitting)., undated; cuid38143 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01096-01 - 01096-31)
  - Individuals - Dennis, Eugene (in suit and tie)., undated; cuid38144 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01097-01 - 01097-06)
  - Individuals - Dennis, Eugene (with family)., undated; cuid38145 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01098-01 - 01098-05)
  - Individuals - Dennis, Eugene (standing on roof)., undated; cuid38146 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01099-01 - 01099-03)
  - Individuals - Dennis, Eugene (in prison cell)., undated; cuid38147 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01100-01)
  - Individuals - Douglass, Frederick., undated; cuid38148 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01101-01)
  - Individuals - Du Bois, W.E.B., undated; cuid38149 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01102-01 - 01102-03)
  - Individuals - Du Bois, W.E.B. - Leaving for Ghana; Shaking Hands with Gus Hall when he joins the Communist Party of the United States of America; With Shirley Du Bois Graham., undated; cuid38150 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01103-01 - 01103-17)
  - Individuals - Elisabeth in Uniform., undated; cuid38151 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01104-01 - 01104-05)
  - Individuals - Fasanella, Ralph - Paintings Exhibit., undated; cuid38152 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01105-01- 01105-03)
  - Individuals - Feuchtwanger, Lion (German writer, refugee) - Arrival of., undated; cuid38153 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01106-01 - 01106-06)
  - Individuals - Fischer, Louis., undated; cuid38154 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01107-01 - 01107-03)
  - Individuals - Flynn, Elizabeth Gurley - Holding "Girls in Uniform" Pamphlet., undated; cuid38155 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01108-01 - 01108-03)
  - Individuals - Ford, James W. - Election Campaign, Arriving in Newark (New Jersey)., undated; cuid38156 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01109-01 - 01109-02)
  - Individuals - Foster, William Z., undated; cuid38157 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01110-01 - 01110-21)
  - Individuals - Foster, William Z. and Grandson Butch., undated; cuid38158 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01111-01 - 01111-02)
  - Individuals - Foster, William Z. - with Model Ship, Waterfront Section., undated; cuid38159 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01112-01 - 01112-02)
  - Individuals - Gannes, Harry, Jr., undated; cuid38160 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01112a-01 - 01112a - 02)
  - Individuals - George, Harrison (editor of People's World)., undated; cuid38161 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01113-01)
  - Individuals - Glicken, Mr., undated; cuid38162 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01114-01 - 01114-02)
  - Individuals - Glicken, Sonia - Arrives from South America from Vacation., undated; cuid38163 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01115-01 - 01115-02)
  - Individuals - Gold, Michael - Speaking at Columbia University., undated; cuid38164 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01116-01 - 01116-03)
  - Individuals - Green, Beulah (Wife of Torpedoed Seaman)., undated; cuid38165 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01117-01)
  - Individuals - Hall, Gus, undated; cuid38166 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01118-01 - 01118-09)
  - Individuals - Hall, Gus., undated; cuid38167 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01119-01)
  - Individuals - Hall, Gus., undated; cuid38168 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01120-01 - 01120-08)
  - Individuals - Hall, Gus.., undated; cuid38169 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01121-01 - 01121-04)
  - Individuals - Hall, Gus - at May Day Celebration in Union Square (New York, New York). (Left to right: Louis Weinstock, Eugene Dennis, Henry Winston, Gus Hall, John Williamson and baby)., undated; cuid38170 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01122-01 - 01122-09)
  - Individuals - Hall, Gus - with Angela Davis., undated; cuid38171 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01123-01)
  - Individuals - Hall, Gus - with Eugene Dennis, Henry Winston and John Williamson., undated; cuid38172 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01124-01 - 01124-08)
  - Individuals - Hamer, Fannie Lou., undated; cuid38173 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01125-01 - 01125-02)
  - Individuals - Hearst, William Randolph - Clay Caricature of., undated; cuid38174 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01126-01 - 01126-02)
  - Individuals - Holiday, Billie - Photos for May Day Demonstration., undated; cuid38175 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01127-01 - 01127-04)
  - Individuals - Howard, Paula., undated; cuid38176 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01128-01 - 01128-04)
  - Individuals - Jean., undated; cuid38177 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01129-001 - 01129-03)
  - Individuals - Johnny and Singer (and Mack)., undated; cuid38178 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01130-01 - 01130-02)
  - Individuals - Kater, H., undated; cuid38179 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01131-01 - 01131-02)
  - Individuals - Kelly, Edward J., undated; cuid38180 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01132-01)
  - Individuals - King, Martin Luther, Jr., undated; cuid38181 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01133-01)
  - Individuals - Larson, Mother., undated; cuid38182 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01134-01 - 01134-04)
  - Individuals - Leadbelly (Huddie Ledbetter)., undated; cuid38183 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01135-01 - 01135-04)
  - Individuals - Lewis, John L., undated; cuid38184 (Box 8c, Shoot-negative 01135A-01 - 01135A-03)
  - Individuals - Lewis, Katherine - Reception for., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01136-01 - 01136-03)
  - Individuals - [Lotker?], A., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01137-01 - 01137-02)
  - Individuals - Lynch, Helen., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01138-01)
  - Individuals - Marcantonio, Vito - Club Activities., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01139-01 - 01138-03)
  - Individuals - Marcantonio, Vito - Election Campaign., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01140-01 - 01140-04)
  - Individuals - Marx, Karl., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01141-01)
  - Individuals - McFerren, John., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01142-01)
  - Individuals - McLevy, Jasper., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01142a-01 - 01142a-02)
  - Individuals - Mildred., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01143-01 - 01143-02)
  - Individuals - Miller, Mrs. - Mayor's Office Reception., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01144-01 - 01144-05)
  - Individuals - Minor, Robert., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01145-01 - 01145-03)
  - Individuals - Monroe, Harry - Birthday Party for His Son., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01146-01 - 01146-09)
  - Individuals - Myers, Frederick N. "Blackie"., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01147-01)
  - Individuals - North, Joe., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01148-01)
  - Individuals - Olga., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01149-01 - 01149-02)
  - Individuals - Olgin, Moissaye Joseph., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01150-01 - 01150-04)
  - Individuals - Olgin, Moissaye Joseph., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01151-01 - 01151-02)
  - Individuals - Olgin, Moissaye Joseph., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01152-01 - 01152-05)
  - Individuals - Peter - photos of, with mask (and house shots)., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01153-01 - 01153-06)
  - Individuals - Phillip, Cyril., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01154-01)
  - Individuals - Red and his Friend., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01155-01 - 01155-03)
  - Individuals - Reed, John., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01156-01)
  - Individuals - [Right?], Tommy - Typing on Typewriter., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01157-01)
  - Individuals - Robeson, Eslanda Goode., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01158-01)
  - Individuals - Robeson, Paul., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01159-01 - 01159-05)
  - Individuals - Robeson, Paul - as Othello., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01160-01 - 01160-02)
  - Individuals - Robeson, Paul - in Soviet Union., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01161-01)
  - Individuals - Robeson, Paul - with Entertainers., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01162-01)
  - Individuals - Robeson, Paul - with Others., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01163-01 - 01163-16)
  - Individuals - Robeson, Paul - with Trade Unionists., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01164-01 - 01164-03)
  - Individuals - Robinson, Duff., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01165-01 - 01165-09)
  - Individuals - Ross, Adolph - Young Communist League., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01166-01)
  - Individuals - Ruth., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01167-01 - 01167-04)
  - Individuals - Schütz, Jupp., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01168-01)
  - Individuals - Sherman, Dr. - Mother of., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01169-01)
  - Individuals - Shields, Art and Sam D., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01170-01)
  - Individuals - Shiga, Yoshio (Secretary of the Political Bureau of the Central Committee of the Communist Party of Japan)., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01171-01 - 01171-02)
  - Individuals - Shirley and Rose in Darkroom., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01172-01)
  - Individuals - Steel, ? (African American Mayor)., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01173-01 - 01173-06)
  - Individuals - Taft, J. and her Co-Candidate for Election., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01174-01 - 01174-07)
  - Individuals - Tessy., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01175-01)
  - Individuals - Tyner, Jarvis., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01176-01 - 01176-04)
  - Individuals - Unidentified African American Artist. (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01177-01 - 01177-06)
  - Individuals - Unidentified African Amercan Chemist from Moscow., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01178-01 - 01178-07)
  - Individuals - Unidentified African American Conductor., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01179-01)
  - Individuals - Unidentified African American Man., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01180-01 - 01180-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified African American Man with Glasses., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01181-01)
  - Individuals - Unidentified African American Man with Moustache., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01182-01 - 01182-03)
  - Individuals - Unidentified African American Man with Moustache., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01183-01 - 01183-03)
  - Individuals - Unidentified African American Musician., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01184-01 - 01184-05)
  - Individuals - Unidentified African American Woman Wearing Roosevelt Pin., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01185-01 - 01185-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified African American Woman., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01186-01 - 01186-03)
  - Individuals - Unidentified African American Woman., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01187-01 - 01187-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified African American Woman., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01188-01 - 01188-03)
  - Individuals - Unidentified African American Woman at Typewriter., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01189-01 - 01189-04)
  - Individuals - Unidentified African American Women Sitting., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01190-01 - 01190-03)
  - Individuals - Unidentified African American Women Sitting at Desk., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01191-01 - 01191-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified African American Women Sitting at Their Desks., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01192-01 - 01192-03)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Artist with His Work., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01193-01 - 01193-04)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Artist with His work., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01194-01 - 01194-05)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Baby., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01195-01 - 01195-04)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Building [Accountant?]., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01196-01)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Child in Crib., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01197-01 - 01197-03)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Family., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01198-01 - 01198-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Family., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01199-01 - 01199-05)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Family., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01200-01 - 01200-05)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Family., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01201-01)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Family of African Americans., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01202-01 - 01202-03)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Family of African Americans., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01203-01 - 01203-04)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Family of African Americans - Birthday Party, Chelsea (New York, New York)., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01204-01 - 01204-09)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Family of African Americans - Older Boy Showering Younger Boy in Sink., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01205-01 - 01205-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Formal Group Shot of Men and One Woman., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01206-01)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Formal Group Shot of Men and Women., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01207-01 - 01207-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Formal Group Shot of Women and Men., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01208-01 - 01208-05)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Young Woman at Typewriter., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01209-01 - 01209-04)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Young Woman from Texas., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01210-01 - 01210-04)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Group of Children., undated (Box 8d, Shoot-negative 01211-01)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Group of Children in School., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01212-01 - 01212-15)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Group of Injured Veterans., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01213-01 - 01213-08)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Group of Italian Laborers., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01214-01 - 01214-04)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Group of Men., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01214a-01)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Group of Men Holding Coin Display Cases., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01215-01 - 01215-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Group of Men Talking in an Office., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01216-01 - 01216-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Group of Men Taking Measurements [in a Laboratory?]., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01217-01 - 01217-06)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Group of Men and Women, Celebrating - One Man being lifted above other Men's Shoulders, Carrying Flowers., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01218-01 - 01218-04)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Group of Musicans and Audience [B Street?] New York, New York., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01219-01 - 01219-04)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Group of People and Hugh O'Neil Buidling (Chelsea, New York City)., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01219A-01 - 01219A-20)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Group of People in Park., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01220-01 - 01220-05)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Group of People in Park with Lake., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01220A-01 - 01220A-15)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Group of People on a Plaza near a Park., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01221-01 - 01221-04)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Group of People on a Ship., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01222-01 - 01222-06)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Group of Women., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01223-01 - 01223-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Group of Two Women and One Man., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01224-01 - 01224-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Group of Women at Jefferson School of Science Listening to a Man Speaking., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01225-01 - 01225-06)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Group of Young Women., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01226-01 - 01226-08)
  - Individuals - Unidentified - Leader of People [People's?] Party of India., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01227-01 - 01227-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01228-01 - 01228-03)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01229-01 - 01229-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01230-01 - 01230-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01231-01 - 01231-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01232-01 - 01232-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01233-01 - 01233-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01234-01)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01235-01)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01236-01)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man - Subject of Daily Worker Feature Story., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01237-01 - 01237-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man - Addressing Crowd., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01238-01 - 01238-05)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man in Clergy Uniform., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01239-01)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man in Glasses., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01240-01 - 01240-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man in Glasses., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01241-01 - 01241-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man in Glasses., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01242-01 - 01242-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man in Glasses., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01243-01 - 01243-03)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man in Office with National Health Digest on Desk., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01244-01 - 01244-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man Sitting on Couch (original caption reads "Win the Peace")., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01245-01 - 01245-04)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man Speaking., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01246-01)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man with Two Girls and a Baby at [B&T/B Street?] Bar., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01247-01 - 01247-04)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man, ["Red Builder Fronk"]., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01248-01 - 01248-03)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man with Moustache. (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01249-01 - 01249-03)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man in Uniform., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01250-01 - 01250-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man in Uniform., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01251-01)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man in Uniform., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01252-01 - 01252-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Man in Uniform., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01253-01 - 01253-03)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Men in Uniform., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01254-01 - 01254-06)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Men in Uniform., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01255-01 - 01255-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Men in Uniform., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01256-01 - 1256-03)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Men in Uniform [policemen?]., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01257-01 - 01257-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Men in Uniform., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01258-01 - 01258-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Mexican Artist with Painting., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01259-01 - 01259-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Pair of Men., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01260-01 - 01260-03)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Pair of Men., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01261-01 - 01261-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Pair of Men., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01262-01 - 01262-03)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Pair of Men Painting Flag for the First of May., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01263-01 - 01263-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Pair of Men Shaking Hands., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01264-01 - 01264-08)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Pair of Men Shaking Hands., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01265-01)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Pair of Men Shaking Hands and One Man Sitting at Desk., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01266-01)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Pair of Men Walking Up the Stairs., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01267-01 - 01267-03)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Pair of Men with Test Rifle and Measuring Device., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01268-01 - 01268-02)
  - Individuals - Unidentified Woman., undated (Box 9a, Shoot-negative 01269-01)